fasttech.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy: FastTech

******

What information do we collect?

**  

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience - we use your email address as a login, a name to greet you with, and your time zone to display appropriate times in the community forums.  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website - we aggregate popular country names to improve service for customers visiting from those countries  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service - the products and quantity your ordered, and the shipping addresses allow agents provide assistance when you contact us  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions - your name, shipping address, and phone number (required only if express shipping carriers are selected) allows shipping of your orders

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails - if you have explicitly opted in the new products mailing list.

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

FastTech operates with full time SSL supporting TLS 1.2 or better. All sensitive payment information such as credit details are transmitted by TLS 1.2 or better to our payment gateway providers. Their databases are only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required tokeep the information confidential. Should you choose to store a card for faster checkout in the future, FastTech will record the last 4 digits of your card number for your future identification. Otherwise, FastTech does not store any of your credit card details.

All transactions are processed on the spot during checkout, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers and are discarded immediately after an order is placed.

**How to access your data stored at FastTech?**  

; Information collected at account registration are accessible via your account's profile page.  
; Information collected when placing orders are accessible via your account's order history page.  
; Information (posts) you made in the public community forums are displayed publicly in the forums.

**How to delete your information collected by FastTech?**

You may contact us to delete information collected. Certain information such as your recent orders, may be required to be kept until the order is delivered in a satisfactory condition. This is in case of potential disputes. Please note that once order information is deleted, your account priority status, royalty points, and warranties may be become voided.

**Do we use cookies?**  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Preferences' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**  

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.fasttech.com/pages/terms-and-conditions>

**Your Consent**  

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018

**Contacting Us**  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.fasttech.com  
Cloud Commerce Systems  
SUITE 704, 555 NATHAN ROAD  
KOWLOON, Hong Kong  
HONG KONG  
support@fasttech.com
